{
    "id": "4ddf6017a3f744438b1e7332eb68b593",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How did these things ..................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came about",
                "come about",
                "come off",
                "came off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "592460e59bfa42b89f0d8a6321632177"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... an old friend of mine yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came on",
                "came across",
                "came to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "22864d10808147bd8dd38e773f51bb50"
        },
        {
            "question": "That question ..................... . before the committee yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came up",
                "came across",
                "came about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5770c4f53ff54035badaea9d021e4069"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was …………………. in the prime of his life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cut out",
                "cut off",
                "cut up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "674c06f3168648c790ef3b9062c4ec88"
        },
        {
            "question": "His wife’s death ...................... terribly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cut him down",
                "cut him up",
                "cut him out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f62f8b1ae4ab4fc0b402435ee8f277d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He seems to be …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well off",
                "pull off",
                "cut off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f1e7a9c9b7a540019ea208641141fe8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "At last the truth .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came up",
                "came out",
                "came off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04df999b2aa8479eb3b5d74000b847fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "His master .....................… an explanation of his conduct.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "called for",
                "called on",
                "called out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0b6ffe72c23544ed967effbfe46bf9f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He found it rather difficult to ………………….. to his views.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bring her up",
                "bring her round",
                "bring her out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "14f723b4bd974157b9bfd447491a4d22"
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother cannot ………………… past events.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "call out",
                "call on",
                "call up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "139d3b94f701480e8308bbcd71510870"
        }
    ]
}